Cho các lớp:
- SinhVien (mã số, họ tên, năm sinh, mã lớp, điểm trung bình) và hàm NhapThongTin(), InThongTin().
- GiaoVien (mã số, họ tên, năm sinh, hệ số lương, chuyên môn) và hàm NhapThongTin(), InThongTin().
Hãy phân tích các lớp SinhVien và GiaoVien để xây dựng lớp Nguoi chứa các điểm chung của 2 lớp này. Từ đó xây dựng các lớp SinhVien, GiaoVien thừa kế từ lớp Nguoi vừa tạo ra.
Hãy viết chương trình như sau:
-----------------------------------------------------------------------
MANAGEMENT PROGRAM STUDENTS AND TEACHERS
1. Enter Students Information.
2. Enter Teachers Information.
3. Display information of Students and Teachers.
4. Search for Students and Teachers by name.
5. Exit program.
Your choose:

 
We have those classes:
- Student (id, full name, year of birth, id of class, average mark) have two methods inputInformation(), showInformation().
- Teacher (id, full name, year of birth, coefficients salary, specialize) have two methods inputInformation(), showInformation().
Let's analyze the Student class and Teacher to build the Person class contains the common points of the two classes. Since then the construction of the Student and Teacher class, inherited from the Person just created.
Please write the following program:
-----------------------------------------------------------------------
MANAGEMENT PROGRAM STUDENTS AND TEACHERS
1. Enter Students Information.
2. Enter Teachers Information.
3. Display information of Students and Teachers.
4. Search for Students and Teachers by name.
5. Exit program.
Your choose:
